brandseye.com 2014-12-17

# Privacy Policy | BrandsEye

BrandsEye respects your privacy and cares how information about you is used and shared. We appreciate your trust in this regard and assure you that we will make every reasonable effort to manage your personal information carefully, securely and sensibly. When visiting and/or interacting with the BrandsEye Site and using the Services (as defined in the BrandsEye Terms and Conditions [BrandsEye Terms and Conditions](http://www.brandseye.com/terms-and-conditions)) you are expressly consenting to the collection, collation, processing or disclosure of your personal information for the purposes and in the manner described in this Privacy Policy without qualification, so please read it carefully.

Information about our customers is an important part of our business. Such information may be collected, collated, processed or disclosed for the purposes set out hereunder. Where we intend using your information for any alternative purpose, we will first obtain your written consent to do so.

We may compile profiles and reports based on your personal information for statistical purposes or to extend our service offering and may freely trade with such profiles and statistical data with other organisations, specifically within the communities created by sites: provided that such profiles and statistical data are not capable of identifying you as an individual, and that they will not contain any sensitive or confidential information about you. Any information shared by us in this regard will be made available to you on request, so that you may monitor our use of information gathered.

You hereby consent to us disclosing your information to third parties for the purposes set out below. However we will never disclose sensitive or confidential information about you to any third party, unless required to do so by operation of the law or with your prior written consent, if it pertains to any transaction or activity between you and the third party facilitated by BrandsEye.

## Your information may be disclosed for the following purposes

**Agents:**

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include analysing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for any other purpose.

**Business transfers:**

In the event of the purchase or restructuring of the whole or part of our business, certain intellectual property, including our customer’s information, may be transferred to another party in the normal course of business.

**Credit purposes:**

If we receive, compile, retain or report any account or personal information pertaining to you or your financial position, we will protect the confidentiality of that information, and in particular, will:

(a) use that information only for a purpose permitted or required in terms of the National Credit Act 34 of 2005 (South Africa), other national legislation or applicable provincial legislation; and

(b) report or release that information only to you, or to another person

  1. to the extent permitted or required by the National Credit Act, other national legislation or applicable provincial legislation; or
  2. as directed by: 
    1.      a.         your instructions; or
    2.      b.         an order of a court or the South African National Credit Tribunal.

You have the right:

(a) to be advised within a prescribed time before any adverse information is reported by us to a credit bureau and to receive a copy of that information upon request;

(b) to inspect any credit bureau file or information concerning you without charge at least once every 12 months, or by court order or at least once within reasonable period after information has been corrected or expunged to check that it has been corrected or removed; and

(c) to challenge the accuracy of the information held and require the credit bureau to investigate the accuracy of any challenged information without charge.

Where you wish to challenge any such information, you may notify the relevant credit bureau within a reasonable time, and the credit bureau will then take reasonable steps to seek credible evidence in support of the challenged information and provide you with a copy of such evidence OR remove the information from its records if it is unable to find such evidence.

Within 20 days of receiving the evidence from the credit bureau, you may initiate a complaint through the National Credit Regulator if you still remain unsatisfied.

Until a challenge has been resolved satisfactorily, a credit bureau may not report challenged information. Failure to abide by any of the above requirements is an offence.

**Where you consent:**

Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you will be used for some other purposes and/or where it might be disclosed to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information by notifying us accordingly.

## We gather the following information via the Site:

**Information provided by you:**

We receive and store any information you enter on Site or provided by you in any other way. You may choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of the many features on our web sites. We use the information that you provide to continually improve our service offering to you by analysing the information and corresponding trends and the like that may be found. The quality of any analysis or activity based on information is of course dependant on the integrity of the information supplied. We reserve the right to verify any information provided by you.

**Information automatically gathered:**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the web site. For example, like many web sites, we use “cookies”, and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses our web sites. The “cookies” often transfer security related information, so this facility must be activated on your browser whilst accessing our web sites or they may malfunction.

**E-mail communications:**

To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from us. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers or to grow our customer base.

**Information from other sources:**

To improve our service offering, we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our information. The more information we have, the more we can tailor our service offering to meet market expectations.

## Acceptable Use

You agree to act responsibly when using the site.

Your use of the site may not be for any purpose that may be illegal in South Africa or within the jurisdiction from which you are accessing the site.

You may not introduce viruses or code with destructive or contaminating properties or any-thing of a nature that may damage, place unreasonable burdens on, or interfere with, the op-eration of the site or the systems on which it runs, nor may you attempt to gain access to any restricted areas of the site without BrandsEye’s permission.

You may not collect any information about other users of the site without their consent.

## Links to other web sites

This site may contain links to third-party web sites. Those sites are independently managed and maintained by such third-party companies or individuals. BrandsEye does not control those linked sites.

BrandsEye bears no responsibilities for any loss or damage caused by using any web sites that are linked to our site and you use such web sites at your own discretion and risk. Please note that other web sites may contain sexually explicit, violent, racist or other types of material which are objectionable or which may be offensive to you, and user discretion is advised.

Additionally, these links do not suggest that BrandsEye holds any special affiliations or associations with the companies or individuals which own, manage, maintain, advertise on, or link to, these sites.
